Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2016
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Partial percussion setup for Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4074.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_057.tif)
- Partial percussion setup for Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4076.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_058.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine with John Smigielski, percussion rehearsing Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4077.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_059.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine with John Smigielski, percussion rehearsing Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4079 composer Josuha Levine John Smiglieski percussion.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_060.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine and Jonathan Hepfer, percussion rehearsing Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4083composer Joshua Levine Jon Hepfer percussion.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_061.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine, Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, Tom Kolor and Jonathan Hepfer, percussion rehearsing Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4086composer Joshua Levine.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_062.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, John Smigielski, Stephen Solook, Jon Hepfer, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4088conductor Matthew Champerlain.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_063.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, John Smigielski, Stephen Solook, Jon Hepfer, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4090 copy.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_064.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, John Smigielski, Stephen Solook, Jon Hepfer, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4090Slee Simnfonietta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_065.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, John Smigielski, Stephen Solook, Jon Hepfer, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4091 Josh Levine composer Christoper Chamberlain conductor Tom kolor Stephen Solook Jon Hepfer percussion John Smigli~1.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_066.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, John Smigielski, Stephen Solook, Jon Hepfer, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Slee Sinfonietta Matthew Chamberlainconductor.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_067.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung gives a lecture at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4094Chinary Ung lecture inBaird Hall.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_068.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung gives a lecture at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4097.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_069.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung gives a lecture at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4101 composer Chinary Ung.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_070.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung gives a lecture at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4103.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_071.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung gives a lecture at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4104.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_072.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung gives a lecture at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4106 copy.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_073.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung gives a lecture at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4110 Chinary Ung lecture.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_074.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor with Ensemble Signal members Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Tom Kolor, percussion, Emlyn Johnson, flute rehearsing Timothy Roy's Chatterbox at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4116 Ensemble Signal Brad Lubman conductor student composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_075.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor with Ensemble Signal members Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Tom Kolor, percussion, Emlyn Johnson, flute rehearsing Timothy Roy's Chatterbox at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4117Signal student composers rehearsal.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_076.tif)
- Student composer Timothy Roy watches as Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Tom Kolor, percussion, Emlyn Johnson, flute rehearse Roy's Chatterbox at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4118student composer rehearsal Ensemble SIGNAL.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_077.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine gives a master class to student composers Bekah Simms, Pierce Gradone, and Samuel Clark-McHale at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4121Joshua Levine master class.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_078.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine gives a master class to student composer Samuel Clark-McHale at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4122composer Joshua Levine master class.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_079.tif)
- Composer Josh Levine gives a master class to student composer Samuel Clark-McHale at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4123 composer Joshua Levine master class.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_080.tif)
- Student composer Timothy Roy watches as Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Tom Kolor, percussion, Emlyn Johnson, flute rehearse Roy's Chatterbox at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4124Ensemble SIGNAL rehearsal student composer.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_081.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta talks with conductor Brad Lubman onstage, with Ensemble Signal members Tom Kolor, percussion, Adrián Sandí, clarinet, Emlyn Johnson, flute, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, and Courtney Orlando, violin rehearse Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4125rehearsal with Enswmble Signal Xavier Beteta.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_082.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta talks with Brad Lubman, conductor, while Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, watches during rehearsal of Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4127student composer Xavier Beteta Ensemble Signal.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_083.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta talks with Brad Lubman, conductor, while Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, watches during rehearsal of Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4128 student composer Xavier Beteta Ensemble SIGNAL copy.jpg Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_084.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta talks with Brad Lubman, conductor, while Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, watches during rehearsal of Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4128 student composer Xavier Beteta Ensemble SIGNAL.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_085.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta coaches Ning Yu, piano, on Beteta's piece GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4130rehearsal student composer with Ensemble SIGNAL.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_086.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta talks with Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Tom Kolor, percussion, Emlyn Johnson, flute during a rehearsal of Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4132rehearsal with Ensemble SIGNAL.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_087.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta watches Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Ning Yu, piano, Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Adrián Sandí, bass clarinet, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Emlyn Johnson, flute rehearse Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4134ensemble SIGNAL rehearsal.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_088.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Ning Yu, piano, Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Adrián Sandí, bass clarinet, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Emlyn Johnson, flute rehearse Xavier Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4135Signal Emsemble rehearsal student composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_089.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Ning Yu, piano, Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Adrián Sandí, bass clarinet, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Emlyn Johnson, flute rehearse Xavier Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4136rehearsal Ensemble SIGNAL Tuesday copy.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_090.tif)
- Student composer Xavier Beteta coaches Courtney Orlando, violin of Ensemble Signal on Beteta's piece GOLEM as Ning yu, piano, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, and Brad Lubman, conductor look on at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4137.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_091.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Ning Yu, piano, Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Adrián Sandí, bass clarinet, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Emlyn Johnson, flute perform Xavier Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4144 Rnsemble Signal concert Tuesday copy.jpg Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_092.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Ning Yu, piano, Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Adrián Sandí, bass clarinet, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Emlyn Johnson, flute perform Xavier Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4144 Rnsemble Signal concert Tuesday.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_093.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Ning Yu, piano, Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Adrián Sandí, bass clarinet, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Emlyn Johnson, flute perform Xavier Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4146Ensemble SIGNAL student composer concert.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_094.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Ning Yu, piano, Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, Adrián Sandí, bass clarinet, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Emlyn Johnson, flute acknowledge applause after performance of Xavier Beteta's GOLEM at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4147student composer concert Ensemble SIGNAL.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_095.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Signal members Ning Yu, piano, Courtney Orlando, violin, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, and Adrián Sandí, clarinet, during performance of Philip Taylor's Sparks at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4148Ensemble SIGNAL concert student composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_096.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher watches as Malla Vivolin, bass flute, and Marko Kassl, accordion rehearse Eimermacher's Kannst du diesen verkehrt fliegenden Vogel sehen? at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4151composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_097.tif)
- Marko Kassl, accordion rehearses Hanna Eimermacher's Kannst du diesen verkehrt fliegenden Vogel sehen? at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4152for composer Hanna Eimermacher .tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_098.tif)
- Tom Kolor, percussion rehearses Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4156.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_099.tif)
- Stephen Solook, percussion rehearses Josh Levine's Four places, many more time at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4157Steve Solook percussion.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_100.tif)
- Jonathan Hepfer, percussion rehearses Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4160.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_101.tif)
- Conductor Matthew Chamberlain performs Josh Levine's Four places, many more times with Tom Kolor, Jonathan Hepfer, Stephen Solook, and John Smigielski, percussion at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Four Places ,many more times by Joshua Levine copy.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_102.tif)
- Conductor Matthew Chamberlain performs Josh Levine's Four places, many more times with Tom Kolor, Jonathan Hepfer, Stephen Solook, and John Smigielski, percussion at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Four Places ,many more times by Joshua Levine.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_103.tif)
- Conductor Matthew Chamberlain performs Josh Levine's Four places, many more times with Tom Kolor, Jonathan Hepfer, Stephen Solook, and John Smigielski, percussion as an audience watches at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer Josh Levine JIB.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_104.tif)
- Conductor Matthew Chamberlain, with Tom Kolor, Jonathan Hepfer, Stephen Solook, and John Smigielski, percussion, acknowledge applause for a performance of Josh Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4170.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_105.tif)
- Conductor Matthew Chamberlain with Tom Kolor, Jonathan Hepfer, Stephen Solook, and John Smigielski, percussion acknowledge composer Josh Levine after a performance of Levine's Four places, many more times at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer Josh Levine.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_106.tif)
- Jonathan Golove and T. J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion perform Hanna Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name LUFTPOST ( 2012) by Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_107.tif)
- Jonathan Golove and T.J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion acknowledge applause for a performance of Hanna Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Jonathan Golove, TJ Borden, Tom Kolor copy.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_108.tif)
- Jonathan Golove, violoncello hugs composer Hanna Eimermacher as T.J. Borden, violoncello and Tom Kolor, percussion watch after a performance of Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Hanna Eimermacher copy.jpg Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_109.tif)
- Jonathan Golove, violoncello hugs composer Hanna Eimermacher as T.J. Borden, violoncello and Tom Kolor, percussion watch after a performance of Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_110.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher, Jonathan Golove and T.J. Borden, violoncello, and Tom Kolor, percussion acknowledge applause after a performance of Eimermacher's Luftpost für L at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Luftpost by composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_111.tif)
- Conductor Matthew Chamberlain performs Josh Levine's Former Selves with Slee Sinfonietta (Tom Kolor, percussion, Jade Conlee, electronics, Magnus Andersson, guitar, Caroline Sonnett, flute, Jean Kopperud, bass clarinet, Courtney Orlando, violin, Jen Baker, trombone, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Kristen Theriault, harp) at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Josh Levine FORMER SELVES ( 2007).tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_112.tif)
- Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti and Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralf Ehlers, viola) perform student compositions in workshop at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4181ARDITTI QUARTET.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_113.tif)
- Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti and Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralf Ehlers, viola) perform student compositions in workshop at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4182 ARDITTI QUARTET.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_114.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher coaches Ensemble Uusinta members Malla Vivolin and Max Savikangas, glass bottles on Eimermacher's Transparenz at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4186 TRANSPARENZy HannaEimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_115.tif)